## Marcos A. Arguijo

marcos.a.arguijo@gmail.com 956-244-3937

Experienced information technology professional with 6+ year's experience in customer-facing positions. Responsible for process, documentation, and resolution of client-reported issues for infrastructure including servers, networking equipment, peripherals, SAN/NAS, LOB equipment, and ERP systems. Heavy drive to ensure client satisfaction, exercise problem-solving skills, deliver detailed case management, and support teams in an immediate working environment and company-wide scale.

### **SKILLS AND SYSTEMS**

CRM SYSTEMS	ERP SYSTEMS	OPERATING AND DATABASE SYSTEMS	PROGRAMMING AND SCRIPTING
<ul><li>SalesForce</li><li>ConnectWise</li></ul>	<ul><li>Sage Intacct</li><li>Oracle</li></ul>	<ul><li>Windows 7/10</li><li>Microsoft SQL Server</li><li>MySQL</li></ul>	<ul> <li>C# (.NET)</li> <li>Cobol</li> <li>Visual Basic</li> <li>HTML</li> <li>CSS</li> <li>JavaScript (jQuery and React)</li> </ul>

#### **EDUCATION**

Texas A&M University, BBA -- Management Information Systems (MIS), May 2014

Overall GPA: 3.4

- Coursework in Information Technology, Computer Applications, and Enterprise IT Management
- Recipient of the Gates Millennium Scholarship provided by the Gates Foundation

The Coding Bootcamp at UT Texas at Austin -- Web Development Bootcamp Certification - Completing September 2020

- Languages: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript
- Projects: Password Generator, Weather Dashboard, Day Planner, Music Recommendation Engine. List will grow with time.
- GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/On-Your-Marc-GO">https://github.com/On-Your-Marc-GO</a>

### **WORK HISTORY**

## **AcctTwo Shared Services**

Houston, TX

**Customer Support Specialist** 

June 2018 - May 2020

- Daily management of customer support tickets in Sage Intacct ERP system including review, resolution, and prompt notification to customer base.
- Test solutions in internal environments, direct and verify support tickets to internal implementation consultants for specific configurations, leverage AcctTwo engineering teams for internally developed
- Escalate issues to internal management as well as Sage Intacct's customer support and engineering teams as needed.
- Regularly follow up and document status on existing tickets through SalesForce.
- Provide timely correspondence with customers and applicable internal staff/management.
- Participated in AcctTwo's internal culture committee, supporting internal team-building and leading initiatives to support well-being of coworkers. Helped develop and administer AcctTwo's internal Step it Up challenge. This challenge was created to promote overall employee wellness and healthy lifestyles outside of the work place.

Truewater. LLC. Houston, TX August 2017 - June 2018

- Provide 1st and 2nd level support for all managed service clients through call center, ConnectWise ticketing system, and online webchat.
- Manage and maintain all client infrastructure assets ranging from, but not limited to: servers, networking equipment (switches, WAP's, firewalls), peripherals, printers/copiers, SAN/NAS, and enduser equipment.
- Regularly provide on-site support and face-to-face interaction with clients to work on project-related tickets and troubleshoot customer issues.
- Cycled through staff rotation for after-hours on-call schedule to assist clients with any issues on a 24/7 basis.
- Regularly participate in NOC-related activities such as network maintenance and preventative infrastructure maintenance (software/hardware upgrades, backups, etc.)
- Created and maintained accurate documentation for all unique client business processes to ensure quick and proper support.
- Conducted weekly meetings related to progress and captured process improvement feedback.

#### Aspen Technology, Inc.

Houston, TX

**Technical Support Consultant** 

May 2017 – July 2017

- Provided technical support and recommendations to customers through telephone, e-mail, and the web.
- Documented all work in internal, proprietary CRM system.
- Drove improvements in AspenTech software's ease of use.
- Captured customer feedback and directed to R&D team to improve products.
- Conducted software deployments as a subject-matter expert and provided technical leadership to other employees.
- Authored white paper solution articles for publication to the user community through web knowledge base.

### **Royal Imagine Services, LLC + Office Gemini**

Houston, TX

Jr. Application Analyst – IT Support Technician

January 2016 - May 2017

- Maintained high level knowledge of all document management software solutions; main products supported include DocuWare and proprietary products Dokmee DMS/Dokmee Capture.
- Provided first line, technical support for software customers and internal organization staff.
- Resolved technical support issues and aided in document management/production scanning.
- Assisted with new customer software deployments and existing customer system upgrades, perform remote and/or onsite installations complete with end-user training and continual post-installation support.
- Actively tested current iterations of proprietary software and recorded all software bugs found.
   Issues pertaining to DocuWare were reported to 2nd party support, while issues pertaining to Office Gemini products were reviewed directly with QA/Development teams.
- Provided continual insight and product development ideas based on feedback received from customer support interactions. Situational information captured used to create, test, and document training use cases.
- Documented all procedures related to regular business processes and internal asset management.

### The Reynolds and Reynolds Company

Houston, TX

**Business Applications Developer** 

August 2014 – September 2015

- Supported and maintained organization's proprietary applications: ERA-IGNITE, ERA ACCESS, and POWER.
- Troubleshooted application issues.
- Developed internal reporting framework for issues found during testing.

- Liaised between programming teams to ensure all applications performed accurately and proficiently.
- Researched and prepared detailed design documentation for all program modifications that were implemented into ERA-IGNITE and POWER application suites.

# Repair Center Technician

July 2013 - August 2014

- Maintained a work schedule of 15-29 hours/week in addition to attending class.
- Repaired employee hardware, including embedded systems and servers.